<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>PyCon Israel 2024 - announcements</title><link href="https://pycon.org.il/2024/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://pycon.org.il/2024/feeds/announcements.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://pycon.org.il/2024/</id><updated>2024-07-25T12:30:00+03:00</updated><subtitle>PyCon Israel is a conference dedicated to the Python programming language, related technologies, and their use.</subtitle><entry><title>PyCon Israel 2024 Tickets Available</title><link href="https://pycon.org.il/2024/tickets-available.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-25T12:30:00+03:00</published><updated>2024-07-25T12:30:00+03:00</updated><author><name>PyCon Israel Team</name></author><id>tag:pycon.org.il,2024-07-25:/2024/tickets-available.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;PyCon Israel 2024 tickets are available to buy&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PyCon Israel is happy to announce that ticket sales are now open, but
before you go there, a few words of explanation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have always strived to keep PyCon Israel ticket prices low, to make
it accessible to a wide audience. In all of the past years, the ticket
price was far below the conference costs per attendee (PyCon Israel is
run by volunteers, and was never intended to make a profit). But most
of the tickets ended up purchased by companies for their employees,
which meant that the conference was subsidizing these companies (with
volunteer work and sponsor money). This never seemed right to us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ve tried to make cheaper tickets available by request, but that
didn’t work – nobody asked for them until the “regular” tickets were
out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this year, we’re trying a different way. We have tickets for
employees, at a price that reflects actual costs to the conference,
and tickets for individuals, at a more accessible price point. We hope
this is not abused, so we can keep the lower price available for
individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One more point – as usual, the workshops are on a separate day, at a
different place; workshop tickets are not valid for the conference
talks day, and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, go &lt;a href="https://ti.to/hamakor/pycon2024"&gt;grab your tickets&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="announcements"></category></entry><entry><title>PyCon Israel 2024 Agenda Published</title><link href="https://pycon.org.il/2024/agenda-published.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-21T22:45:00+03:00</published><updated>2024-07-21T22:45:00+03:00</updated><author><name>PyCon Israel Team</name></author><id>tag:pycon.org.il,2024-07-21:/2024/agenda-published.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The PyCon Israel 2024 agenda is out&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;PyCon Israel is proud to present the agenda for the 2024 conference.
This agenda is the result of long hours of work -- by the submitters
of proposals which were chosen, and proposals which weren't;
by &lt;a href="https://pycon.org.il/2024/meet-pyconil-reviewers.html"&gt;reviewers&lt;/a&gt;,
and by the conference team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The agenda includes an opening panel, 27 talks and five workshops. We
believe it reflects our commitments to excellent content and to the
local community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go &lt;a href="https://pycon.org.il/2024/pages/schedule.html"&gt;check it out&lt;/a&gt;! We expect
tickets to be available later this week.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="announcements"></category></entry></feed>